damages and criminal acts by man life
insurance company part
seven 2018 interaction via emails
between Adrian nicolini sib lawyer and
man life insurance also provided
information to Adrian nicolini due to
the deception of man life insurance and
B Mobility um man life insurance placed
my job on the line so I kept um Adrian
nicoline informed I felt comfortable
with Adrian nicolini's involvement right
wsib lawyer since he was able to respond
effec L to man life insurance and the
Mobil lawyer right I did not realize it
was all an act I thought it was genuine
okay so Adrian nicolini nicolini Law
Firm um he was a wsib lawyer um he
started to respond to man life on my
behalf in January 2018
okay so
here January 16
2018 um man life had included Adrian
Nini because he responded to man life
okay and man I I don't really want to
read I don't want to read it's got a lot
of the information here man life um has
been provided us incorrect information
okay it was more in favor of V Mobility
so anything they say it's actually
misconstrued okay Sol benefits were
orientated in January salary retroactive
I got it retroactive back to November
2017 right and I started Physiotherapy
on January 10th okay and
here Ashlin steel right um based off
what man life request was and all that
ashin steel on January 17th responded
ashin steel is um one of uh the
legal um person there at nickol Law Firm
okay she's one of nicolini Law's
representative okay um
so ashleen responded kindly find
attached Dr
silverberg um report Dr silverberg's
reported in November 17th 2017 just
letting you know again that man life
insurance is has been
[Music]
um has been um ignoring that's the word
ignoring Dr Silver Bird's report so I
guess the lawyer here recognized that
based on the information here January 16
that man life of um um included
so here was a response and she uh
ashleen steel provided the report again
to man life okay it was attached all
right please ref you to pause and read
okay because in this in the meantime
here she was actually defending me okay
I will just read what highlighted in
green Dr silverberg's report is quite
clear that Miss Grant is unable to
return to Earth pre- disability duties
at this time and then it says in
addition as you will note Dr
silverberg's November 2017 2017 report
November 17 2017 report um he indicates
that even with a local cortisone
injection she would not be suitable to
return to pre-
disability um duties but life was
so um forceful telling me that I need to
take the cordone injection they want to
actually damage me if we don't you see
if you don't know you're right if you
don't know yourself and know that
they're telling you to do wrong you will
follow them and then you're the one who
suffer later on and that's what they
wanted the I didn't the in the cortisol
injection would not have helped me okay
please ref you to pause and read thank
you and I this is my little thing I put
through put um put together um about
manone life manone life insurance the
can Canan Human Rights Act and you can
read if you can and criminal act please
read the deception man life insurance
company continued to so obvious that man
life insurance
involvment influen the medical system
okay please feel free to read this is a
summary of things that man life did so
we know definitely that man life was
either the company's racist or the
company is just it does it to
everyone so that a company will not pay
out um to an injured person or whatever
you understand so whatever it is it's
still defying still violating the kenned
and human rights act
okay deception of the physiotherapy
Clinic continues 2018 brandton
Physiotherapy and the wellness Institute
cered by man life insurance to the start
my clinical not January 2018 to March
2018 I actually started this bton
physiotherapy clinic in in um on the 2
3rd of March 2017 as you could see but
um Mone life did not get the time to
just start my medical records then
instead they seize my benefits okay so I
went back to the clinic cuz I think the
clinic had everything the clinic had
everything thing exercise um I I was
getting exercise for my hand I was
getting uh um the Des treatment um what
they put on my hand and all that not a
not a paper tow will like quality care
right this Clinic was well equipped so I
trusted them Bible say trust no one but
I did I trusted them um in 2017 so I
went back to them in 2018 when I was
when I um benefits was reinstated
okay however I showed you this before
that they dist started when uh money
life now got to them okay money life got
to them there was a planning process so
um they I had a different um
physiotherapist the physiotherapist I
had in um La in 2017 march to April 2017
was really nice and really good you know
however I had this time Rohit Sony and I
could tell something was wrong I could
tell I could I actually felt it I could
tell
that um he was deceitful I could tell it
I could see it in his eyes actually
anyway here it was proof that the it
this was transposed right the letters
then when I got um my brace because he
was the one at first recommended that I
get a new brace and that um I need T I
need a ten machine to take home so I can
use a t machine at night so he said he's
going to request it I didn't he said
he's going to request it okay um so on
February
21st the um man life sent a brace but it
was a left the left side the left brace
you see it was clear for them e you see
it still could like be a the r but you
see it bright enough to form the L as
you can see my injuries was right hand
Deen avitis and left hand lateral
but a clearer view of the letter from
money life insurance
okay left okay here it is left manock
Rizo wrist
brace okay please be free to pause and
read thank
you the of the physiotherapy Clinic
continues there was a plan in place by
man life but BMT physiotherapy did not
submit a request for the right hand new
new brace immediately after the left
brace was returned right they said they
were going to do it and I think
something started um in March on March
7th
2018 right but realize that it was
submitted exactly one month later why
did they take so long e March 21st 2018
my life insurance species what the
reason man and Life Insurance Specialist
I've realized right was a reason for the
delay so as to deny my injury and
benefits okay request submitted again to
man life insurance but with another
trans position of the letters
okay here it is so this was submitted in
January okay this was it and if you
notice the difference okay submitted
March 21st 2018 luckily I I am a person
who love I am keeping records right so I
got this in this this um I asked for a
copy of the um my report and this is
what I got
when I was in when I was at the clinic
so right there the receptionist handed
me this so receive copy of the report at
clinic in 2018 then for whatever was
going on in 2019 I decided I couldn't
find I couldn't find my copy thank God I
couldn't find my copy cuz I didn't
realize that there was a change again in
March it was when I asked um via email I
called actually called and asked for a
copy they said they will send it via
email email which I received a copy via
email on February 26 2019 I feel I got a
copy of the report again and thank God I
found the one that I got in House at the
clinic right and then I was thinking I
let me put aside but then I recognize
something they're different they are
different as you can see okay trying to
transposition and intend to deceive okay
please feel feel free to review thank
thank
you and it continues here it shows that
um it's my right hand okay yet it says
chronic left DEC vein this is right hand
they have chronic left decra vein okay
um tenness nides since June um 2016
right and then they said here that I
wear a right thumb brace so if it's left
if if it's left why am I wearing a right
thumb brace okay so as you can see they
are trying to the the the transposition
here new submission March 2018 which is
also transposed
okay feel feel free to pause and
read and here I've already summarized
the same thing so you can pause and read
if you wish okay I've already went I've
already gone through um I've already
explained actually okay so please be you
to pause and read okay you see
this and you see that they are different
okay thank you